Next week, we're setting the rights pocket.
We call it an order that you might as well especially utility authority board meeting from Monday to June 5th 2023 in case
supposed be going on with these not here at Christy Wondon?
The duties is some of your scouting
Heavenly Father where thankful for You and were grateful
For way they provide for us
the discussion and decisions had here tonight will be guided by you
in being made into best interest to the city's,
In your name we pray.
Amen?
A little bit of a vision
To apply
I'm the United States as America
I do remember
Probably for which it stands
One Nation
Another God
Any other person who would have been
a team just before
Four public input on scheduled personal appearances
Five volumes list
Make them much more proof
Second
5,5.
Minutes for May 15
or your meeting in may 223 special
Motion
$5.50 in 50 cents?
Mayor, members of the Council
In your packet you have an invoice
as are stated for good health strategy
and these professional services were incurred
from March 21st to 2023
April 20th
The majority
These services rendered
a review
response
To emails
Today was right
to main
And city administrators
Review
Fork filings
Once
Once the approval of this is made
If Councils are chooses
That would leave a balance
in our budget for these types
Of claims
$334,822
And 34 cents
For fiscal year which we're
In The final month
At This Fiscal Year Budget
Post-Aprouth
Second
No items?
Aye
So,
Hi
Sumber
Say
Parker
Aye
Eight
Tips
Take claim from
The Ocer River 2D
Modeling
In the amount of $27,350
So
Like The
invoice before
We have a claim
Out there today
This is for
Tehrotec
Um
this was Fork
The Ocer River
ToD Modeling
Which
Is A Primary Engineering effort
Of
This period
Again February 25th
This time
Through April 21st
As well as additional communications
Today we're right to main
Good-Oll Stratton Edmonds in
The city itself
With the payment of this
27,000 and $3.50
That would leave
This City with a
Budget Balance
For
This Fiscal Year
Debtispect
Is A Last Long
Of
This
Don't believe we have any more to do on
ToD Modeling
So I can imagine that there
There
Much Off effort but
Might be some smaller ones
Just for
Communications
Because
We've been reviewing
A lot of the filings that have been happening
Make a motion we approve
Second
Step
Aye
For you
Go for it
Aye
December
Same
Parter
Okay
November 9
We will skip
Number nine
Of The MSUA
And do It
In accordance with
number Nine
in
Reversive Council
Lead
So
If I wanted
TN
Which is Crawford
and Associates
Engagement Letter
For carrying services
On this year
Pendingly
Will Reviews
Christy
So this is the, I'm presenting an effect for Jennifer which in that night. She's still having trouble speaking clearly so
This was a accounting firm
That we used to do our
Help us with their audits and
Our financial statements
And things such as
Let see action here
Trying not understand it says pending legal review
Wouldn't you review at first?
We vote on it.
So then should we not get
It's a test from the auditor to see if
I'm going do this right
Social, so shall
Should be table until
Can me fully vetted?
Well their current contract expires at
The end of
This fiscal year
You have reviewed back
Before
That was as table is
Thank you for the
Thank You for your time.
We're going to be table 11
Provide contract agreement with republic services
Be advised waste systems of Missouri
For tipping fees, solid ways
Disposed Mr Brown breath
Yeah we had
I don't know if you guys had a chance to
Look at this much but
The changes that we
We changed from city of my
Myem and
Especially utility authority.
Now start having good understanding
And
We change for April 12th
To april 30
On the second line
We have a meeting
The second line
We are going to be in the middle of
A section, termination prior
To end
And we didn't really see any need
I think both parties after visiting
We want contract
To move on and
We've got an understanding
If somebody has
We're going to be in the middle of
A section, we have a meeting
We are not being reasonably with help
Delayed or conditioned by city
With
The cellar purchase business
I thought that was interesting
It seems like
You know
The giants keep fighting off more and
More people
And then the last part
They wanted to add
The definitions of how they
Generally
Define all
All different type ways that there are
I asked about
We didn't have
Definitions, we had
You
Have two advice
They said, yeah
That means all of the things that we're doing now
And then there's a force measure at
The base and course
Course measures
If
There is acts
Of God or things it happened
It could affect
Probably for a limited amount of time
Depending on how long
So
We reviewed
The contract as it was originally submitted
You all approved
After that
They came in
Requesting
So these changes
In return
That are built into this
Technically
after they did something
There is no doubt to change
But we don't really find any objections
To any of the things
I think it helps both parties
So being in
It's going to say that
Usually beneficial
They are very all concerned
We're given for a way test
There was no pricing changes or anything like
That would affect cost
I can motion we approve
Hi
Number 12
Command Resolution
CC 2023
Dash 9
The City of Miami
The Board Trust ease
For a community financial support
And way we're pleased for a
Millie's fine first in the clients
For a contract
So these are
This is
We've brought before you for several other
Businesses that are locating here in our community
So it's a labor of
Permits and inspection fees
But not the actual inspection
That needs to take place or pulling
The permit
And then,
Then
The labor on
Rolloff
If your driven down main
You can see they have already started
Thank you
The new business spending which is a
Businesses, the Posting of this agenda
14. Trust that you can meet in Ausland
So it's going on to turn